Ford Foundation records, Building Services, Ford Foundation artwork photographs FA1723
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Artwork photograph files, 1963-1969, 2019; 1; 2.66 Cubic Feet About 7 LTR size Hollinger boxes
  - Lecomte, Paul - St. Servan, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 110)
    Art description: Paul Lecomte (French, 1842-1920) St. Servan Watercolor and pencil, 7 3/4 x 11" Purchased from Mrs. Walter Feilchenfeldt, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Louis, Victor - Design for a Proposed Triumphal Arch at the Town of Marseilles, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photograph negatives. (Box 4, Folder 111)
    Art description: Victor Louis (French, 1731-1800) Design for a Proposed Triumphal Arch at the Town of Marseilles, 1784 Pen and colored wash. 17 3/8 x 23 1/2" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Lucas, Claude - Plan of Paris, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 112)
    Art description: Claude Lucas (French, circa 1710-1760) (after Louis Bretez) Plan of Paris, 1739 Engraving, 100 x 127" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Luce, Maximilien - Le Camaret, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 113)
    Art description: Maximilien Luce (French, 1858-1941) Le Camaret Pencil, 8 3/4 x 11 3/4" Purchased from Hector Brame, Paris, France
  - Martin, Elias - The Pont Royal, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 114)
    Art description: Elias Martin (Swedish, 1739-1818) The Pont Royal, circa 1810 Gouache, 28 3/4 x 20 1/4" Purchased from M. Knoedler, New York, New York
  - Martin, Elias - View of the Chateau of St. Cloud with the Lantern of Demosthenes, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 115)
    Art description: Elias Martin (Swedish, 1739-1818) View of the Chateau of St. Cloud with the Lantern of Demosthenes, circa 1810 Gouache, 28 3/4 x 20" (Sight) Purchased M. Knoedler, New York, New York
  - Matisse, Henri - Danseuse refletee dans la glace, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 116)
    Art description: Henri Matisse (French, 1869-1954) Danseuse refletee dans la glace, 1927 Lithograph, 20 1/2 x 14 1/4" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Matisse, Henri - Still Life, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 117)
    Art description: Henri Matisse (French, 1869-1954) Still Life, 1944 Pen and ink, 20 1/2 x 15 3/4" Purchased from Mrs. Walter Feilchenfeldt, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Merlo, Giovanni and Stefano Scolari - View of Venice, 1967-1968; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and photograph negatives. (Box 4, Folder 118)
    Art description: Giovanni Merlo and Stefano Scolari (Italian, 17th Century) View of Venice, 1660 Engraving, 32 x 62 3/4" Purchased from August Laube, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Meryon, Charles - San Francisco, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 119)
    Art description: Charles Meryon (French, 1821-1868) San Francisco, 1855 Etching, 8 3/4 x 39 3/4" Purchased from John Howell, San Francisco, California
  - Meunier, Constantin - Seated Miner, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 120)
    Art description: Constantin Meunier (Belgian, 1831-1905) Seated Miner Bronze, 15" high Purchased from H.L. Shickman, New York, New York
  - Minami, Keiko - La Cygne noire, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 121)
    Art description: Keiko Minami (Japanese, born 1911) La Cygne noire Color etching, 11 3/4 x 11 3/4" Purchased from L'Art Ancien, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Minami, Keiko - L'Arbre fond beige, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 122)
    Art description: Keiko Minami (Japanese, born 1911) L'Arbre fond beige Color etching, 11 1/2 x 11 1/2" Purchased from L'Art Ancien, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Minami, Keiko - L'Arbre fond vert, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 123)
    Art description: Keiko Minami (Japanese, born 1911) L'Arbre fond vert Color etching, 11 1/2 x 11 1/2" Purchased from L'Art Ancien, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Minami, Keiko - Deux oiseaux perches, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 124)
    Art description: Keiko Minami (Japanese, born 1911) Deux oiseaux perches Color etching, 11 1/2 x 11 1/2" Purchased from L'Art Ancien, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Minami, Keiko - Deux oiseaux reposant, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 125)
    Art description: Keiko Minami (Japanese, born 1911) Deux oiseaux reposant Color etching, 11 1/2 x 15 1/2" Purchased from L'Art Ancien, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Minami, Keiko - La petite bergere, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 126)
    Art description: Keiko Minami (Japanese, born 1911) La petite bergere Color etching, 11 1/2 x 11 1/2" Purchased from L'Art Ancien, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Miro, Joan - Composition, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 127)
    Art description: Joan Miro (Spanish, born 1893) Composition, 1958 Color woodcut, 20 1/2 x 14 1/2" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Miro, Joan - Color lithographs, 1967; File contains still images. Images consists of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 4, Folder 128)
    Art description: Joan Miro (Spanish, born 1893) - La Cascade, 1966 Color lithograph, 35 1/2 x 24" - Pierrot le Fou, 1966 Color lithograph, 35 1/2 x 24" - Le Vendangeur, 1966 Color lithograph, 35 1/2 x 24" - Les Guetteurs, 1966 Color lithograph, 35 1/2 x 24" - L'Anneau du Crepuscule, 1966 Color lithograph, 35 1/2 x 24" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Moitte, Jean Guillaume - Design for a Garden with a Temple and Fountains, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 129)
    Art description: Attributed to Jean Guillaume Moitte (French, 1746-1810) Design for a Garden with a Temple and Fountains Pen, ink, and watercolor, 23 3/4 x 81 1/2" Purchased from Sven Gahlin, London, United Kingdom
  - Moll, Herman - A New and Exact Map of the Dominions of the King of Great Britain on ye Continent of North America, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 130)
    Art description: Herman Moll (English ?, 18th Century) A New and Exact Map of the Dominions of the King of Great Britain on ye Continent of North America, 1715 Colored map, 42 x 25" Purchased from John Howell, San Francisco, California
  - Moore, Henry - Studies for Sculpture, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 131)
    Art description: Henry Moore (English, born 1898) Studies for Sculpture, 1935 Pencil on Board, 14 7/8 x 21 3/4" Purchased from Hanover Gallery, London, United Kingdom
  - Nash, Joseph - Opening of the Great Exhibition, London, 1967; File contains still images. Images consists of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 4, Folder 132)
    Art description: Joseph Nash (English, 1808-1878) Opening of the Great Exhibition, London, 1851 - Plate 1: The Inauguration Color Lithograph, 21 1/2 x 30" - Plate 2: The Foreign Nave Color Lithograph, 22 x 29 1/2" - Plate 3: The British Nave Color Lithograph, 21 1/2 x 29 1/2" - Plate 4: The Transept Color Lithograph, 21 1/2 x 29 1/2" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Nash, Paul - Cumulous Clouds, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 133)
    Art description: Paul Nash (English, 1889-1946) Cumulous Clouds Watercolor, 13 x 20 1/2" Purchased from Thos. Agnew and Sons, London, United Kingdom
  - Nash, Paul - Toulon Harbour, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 134)
    Art description: Paul Nash (English, 1889-1946) Toulon Harbour Watercolor, 13 1/4 x 19 3/4" Purchased from Ernest Brown and Phillips, London, United Kingdom
  - Naudet, Charles - Street scene in Paris with a group of Savoyards and their performing dogs, 1966-1969; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 135)
    Art description: Charles Naudet (French, 1773-1810) Street scene in Paris with a group of Savoyards and their performing dogs Pen, watercolor, and gouache Purchased from Bernard Houthakker, Amsterdam, Netherlands
  - Netherlands, Anonymous, circa 1400 - Antiphonal leaves, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 5, Folder 136)
    Art description: Netherlands, Anonymous, circa 1400 - Antiphonal leaf: The Nativity On vellum, 20 1/2 x 13 3/4" - Antiphonal leaf: The Adoration of the Magi On vellum, 20 1/2 x 13 3/4" - Antiphonal leaf: The Annunciation On vellum, 20 1/2 x 13 3/4" - Antiphonal leaf: The Presentation in the Temple On vellum, 20 1/2 x 13 3/4" Purchased from Philip C. Duschnes, New York, New York
  - Nicholson, Ben - Olympia, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 137)
    Art description: Ben Nicholson (English, born 1894) Olympia, 1965 Ink and oil wash, 14 1/2 x 12 3/4" (Sight) Purchased from Gimpel and Hanover, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Nicholson, Ben - Urbino, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 138)
    Art description: Ben Nicholson (English, born 1894) Urbino, 1965 Ink and oil wash, 15 x 12 3/4" (Sight) Purchased from Gimpel and Hanover, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Nolde, Emil - Grossbauern, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 139)
    Art description: Emil Nolde (German, 1867-1956) Grossbauern Etching, 9 x 12" Purchased from L'Art Ancien, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Nolde, Emil - Head of a Negro Woman, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 140)
    Art description: Emil Nolde (German, 1867-1956) Head of a Negro Woman Watercolor, 19 x 14" (Sight) Purchased from H.L. Schickman, New York, New York
  - Nolli, Giambattista - Map of Rome, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 141)
    Art description: Giambattista Nolli (Italian, 1692-1756) Map of Rome, 1748 Engraving, 69 x 81 1/2" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Pechstein, Max - Italian Harbour, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 142)
    Art description: Max Pechstein (German, 1881-1955) Italian Harbour, 1913 Pen, 14 1/2 x 19 1/2" Purchased from L'Art Ancien, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Perelle (family of), French, 17th Century - Pine Trees, 1965-1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative (Box 5, Folder 143)
    Art description: Perelle (family of), French, 17th Century Pine Trees Pen, 10 1/2 x 9 1/2" Purchased from Bernard Houthakker, Amsterdam, Netherlands
  - Perrot, Ferdinand Victor - St. Petersbourg lithographs, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 5, Folder 144)
    Art description: Ferdinand Victor Perrot (French, 1808-1841) - St. Petersbourg: Academie des Beaux-Arts Color lithograph, 10 1/4 x 14 3/4" - St. Petersbourg: Palais d'Hiver Color lithograph, 11 x 18" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Picasso, Pablo - Peintre chauve devant son chevalet, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 145)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Peintre chauve devant son chevalet, 1927 Etching, 9 x 11" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Picasso, Pablo - L'Abeille, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 146)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) L'Abeille, 1936 Etching, 12 1/4 x 8 1/4" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France File also contains a photograph of Street Scene, Moscow by Alfred Gomersal Vickers
  - Picasso, Pablo - Composition in trois couleurs, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 147)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Composition in trois couleurs, 1947 Color lithograph, 8 x 11" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Picasso, Pablo - Carmen, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 148)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Carmen, 1949 Aquatint, 29 1/2 x 15" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Picasso, Pablo - Troupe d'acteurs, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 149)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Troupe d'acteurs, 1954 Lithograph, 19 3/4 x 25 7/8" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Picasso, Pablo - Le Peintre sur la Plage, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 150)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Le Peintre sur la Plage, 1955 Aquatint, 18 3/4 x 33" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Picasso, Pablo - Femme a la blouse a fleurs, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 151)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Femme a la blouse a fleurs, 1957-1958 Lithograph, 25 x 19" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Picasso, Pablo - Femme accoudee, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 152)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Femme accoudee, 1959 Linoleum engraving, 25 x 21" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Picasso, Pablo - Picador et cheval, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 153)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Picador et cheval, 1959 Linoleum engraving, 25 1/4 x 21" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Picasso, Pablo - Pique, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 154)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Pique, 1959 Linoleum engraving, 21 x 25 1/4" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Picasso, Pablo - Corrida, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 155)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Corrida, 1961 Lithograph, 26 x 19 3/4" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Picasso, Pablo - Nature-morte a la pasteque, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 156)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Nature-morte a la pasteque, 1962 Color linoleum engraving, 24 1/2 x 29 1/2" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Picasso, Pablo - Fumeur, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 157)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Fumeur, 1964 Original color aquatint, 16 3/8 x 12 7/16" Purchased from Galerie Rosengart, Lucerne, Switzerland
  - Picasso, Pablo - Dans l'atelier, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 158)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Dans l'atelier, 1965 - Original aquatint, 10 5/8 x 14 3/4" Purchased from Galerie Rosengart, Lucerne, Switzerland - Aquatint and drypoint, 9 5/8 x 15" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Picasso, Pablo - Dans l'atelier, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 159)
    Art description: Pablo Picasso (Spanish, born 1881) Dans l'atelier, 1965 - Aquatint and drypoint, 9 5/8 x 15" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France Photograph that corresponds to the negative is housed in Picasso, Pablo – Dans l'atelier, 1966, Box 5, Folder 158
  - Pine, John - A Plan of the Cities of London and Westminster, 1967; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 160)
    Art description: John Pine (English, 1690-1756) (after a survey by John Rocque) A Plan of the Cities of London and Westminster and borough of Southwark …, 1746 Engraving, 81 x 153" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Piranesi, Giovanni Battista - Carceri d'Invenzione, 1966; File contains still images. Images are photograph negatives. (Box 5, Folder 161)
    Art description: Giovanni Battista Piranesi (Italian, 1720-1778) Carceri d'Invenzione, 1750 16 etchings Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Pope, Clara Maria - White and Red Camellias, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 162)
    Art description: Clara Maria Pope (English, 1750-1838) White and Red Camellias, 1819 Color aquatint, 23 x 18 1/2" Purchased from August Laube, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Preston, W. - A View of the Cove and Part of Sydney, New South Wales, Taken from Dawe's Battery, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 163)
    Art description: Preston, W. (British, 19th Century) A View of the Cove and Part of Sydney, New South Wales, Taken from Dawe's Battery (after Captain Wallis, 46th Regiment), 1820 Engraving, 15 1/4 x 22 3/4" Purchased from John Howell, San Francisco, California
  - Rennenkampff, P. da - Odessa, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 164)
    Art description: P. da Rennenkampff (German, 19th Century) Odessa, 1851 Pencil, 13 1/2 x 17 3/4" Purchased from August Laube, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Rippl-Ronai, Josef - La Fete au village, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 165)
    Art description: Josef Rippl-Ronai (Hungarian, 1861-1927) La Fete au village, 1896 Color lithograph, 16 1/2 x 21" Purchased from L'Art Ancien, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Rossini, Luigi - Veduta della gran traviata della Basilica si S. Pietro in Vaticana, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 166)
    Art description: Luigi Rossini (Italian, 1790-1857) Veduta della gran traviata della Basilica si S. Pietro in Vaticana. Roma 1832 Pen and wash, 24 x 34 5/8" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Rouault, Georges - Le Jongleur, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 167)
    Art description: Georges Rouault (French, 1871-1958) Le Jongleur, 1930 Color aquatint, 12 1/4 x 8 1/2" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Rouault, Georges - Clown vert, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 168)
    Art description: Georges Rouault (French, 1871-1958) Clown vert, 1930 Color aquatint, 12 x 8 1/4" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Rouault, Georges - Danseuse, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 169)
    Art description: Georges Rouault (French, 1871-1958) Danseuse, 1930 Color aquatint, 12 x 8" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Rouault, Georges - L'Ecuyere, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 5, Folder 170)
    Art description: Georges Rouault (French, 1871-1958) L'Ecuyere, 1930 Color aquatint, 11 3/4 x 9" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Rowe, George - View of the City of Melbourne, From the Observatory, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 6, Folder 171)
    Art description: George Rowe (British, 19th Century) View of the City of Melbourne, From the Observatory Lithograph, 20 1/2 x 29" Purchased from John Howell, San Francisco, California
  - Rowlandson, Thomas - La Place des Victoires, Paris, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 6, Folder 172)
    Art description: Thomas Rowlandson (English, 1756-1827) La Place des Victoires, Paris, 1789 Hand-colored etching with aquatint, 13 7/8 x 21" Purchased from R.E. Lewis, San Francisco, California
  - Rowlandson, Thomas - The Prospect Before Us, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 6, Folder 173)
    Art description: Thomas Rowlandson (English, 1756-1827) The Prospect Before Us, 1791 Hand-colored etching with aquatint, 12 x 18" (plus text and margins) Purchased from R.E. Lewis, San Francisco, California
  - Russo-Polish School, 19th Century- An Incident in the Campaign of 1812, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 6, Folder 174)
    Art description: Russo-Polish School, 19th Century An Incident in the Campaign of 1812 Watercolor, 9 1/8 x 18 5/16" Purchased from Yvonne Ffrench, London, United Kingdom
  - Rymer, William C. - Hacienda San Miguel watercolors, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 6, Folder 175)
    Art description: William C. Rymer (American?, active 1870-1880) - Hacienda of San Miguel, Batopilas, Mexico, 1874 Watercolor, 15 5/8 x 22 1/4" (Sight) - San Miguel Tunnel and Mines, Batopilas, Mexico, 1874 Watercolore, 14 7/8 x 21 3/4" (Sight) Purchased from Kennedy Galleries, New York, New York
  - Sachs, Hans - Broadsheet. "Die Zwelff Eygenschafft eines boszhafftigen verruchten weybs", 1967; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 6, Folder 176)
    Art description: Hans Sachs (German, 1494-1576) Broadsheet. "Die Zwelff Eygenschafft eines boszhafftigen verruchten weybs" (The twelve characteristic peculiarities of a malicious wicked wife) Color woodcut, 21 1/2 x 15 1/4" Purchased from August Laube, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Saint-Aubin, Augustin de - La Famille du Prince de Conti, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 6, Folder 177)
    Art description: Augustin de Saint-Aubin (French, 1737-1807) La Famille du Prince de Conti Pencil, 9 3/4 x 14 3/4" (Sight) Purchased from Hector Brame, Paris, France The photograph that corresponds to the negative in the file can be found in Miscellaneous artwork, 1967-1968, Box 7, Folder 224-225
  - Scaglia, Leonardo - Drawing of a Fortification, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 6, Folder 178)
    Art description: Leonardo Scaglia (Italian, born France, 17th Century, active 1640-1650_ Drawing of a Fortification - No. 1 (page No. 72) - No. 2 (page No. 66) - No. 3 (page No. 65) - No. 4 (page No. 60) Pen and wash. 6 1/4 x 8 1/4" Purchased from Christopher Powney, London, United Kingdom